Guide to the Penn State Extension records 01131
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
- 10: Records
  - Task Narratives #1-98, 1974; cuid2335; 1 Items (Box 133)
  - Task Narratives #1-98, 1975; cuid2336; 1 Items (Box 130)
  - Task Narratives #1-98, 1977; cuid2337; 1 Items (Box 134)
  - Task Narratives #1-98, 1978; cuid2338; 1 Items (Box 135)
  - Task Narratives #2-97, 1979; cuid2339; 1 Items (Box 123)
  - Task Narratives #2-98, 1980; cuid2340; 1 Items (Box 127)
  - Task Narratives #2-98, 1981; cuid2341; 1 Items (Box 156)
  - Task Outlines by Use Code, 1974; cuid2342; 1 Items (Box 139)
  - Teachers' Institute in Landscape Horticulture, 1966/07; cuid2343; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Teaching Instruction, 1927-1965; cuid2344; 1 Items (Box 172)
  - Textiles and Clothing, undated; cuid2345; 1 Items (Box 179)
    4-H Guide Sheets
  - Think Great Drinks…, undated; cuid2346; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Three Squares a Day, undated; cuid2347; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Time Distribution Bound Volume, 1926-1968; cuid2348; 1 Items (Box 153)
  - To Celebrate the Bounty of this Good Earth, undated; cuid2349; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Town and Country Business Program - Leader's Guides and Member's Guides, undated; cuid2350; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - Trainees in the Peace Corps, Maharashtra, India - Animal Husbandry Program, undated; cuid2351; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Training Apple and Peach Trees, undated; cuid2352; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Trees and Our Environment - Fourth Annual Pennsylvania Shade Free Symposium, 1969/01; cuid2353; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Turfgrass Chemical Weed Control, undated; cuid2354; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Turfgrass Weed Control, undated; cuid2355; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Twenty Years Ago - Portrait of Change: Northeastern Regional Association Summer Meeting, undated; cuid2356; 1 Items; Photographic--Prints (Box 178)
  - Twenty-four Years Later: Migration and Success, 1980/03; cuid2357; 1 Items (Box 175)
  - Undergraduate Program in Food Science at Penn State, undated; cuid2358; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Unique Approach to the Problems of Poverty in Rural Pennsylvania - The Rural Planning Specialist Project, undated; cuid2359; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - UniSCOPE, 2000 (Box 277)
  - Unit Demonstration Farms, 1959-1965; cuid2360; 1 Items (Box 106)
  - Urban Agriculture Committee - Program Impact Summary, 2004 (Box 277)
  - Urban Agriculture Policy Notebook, 2003; cuid2419 (Box 236)
  - Urban Gardening Information, 1986-1990; cuid2361 (Box 191)
  - USDA Annual Reports, undated; cuid2362; 1 Items (Box 117)
  - USDA correspondence, 1999-2005 (Box 278)
  - USDA correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 277)
  - USDA History Material, undated; cuid2363; 1 Items (Box 121)
  - USDA Publications, undated; cuid2364; 1 Items (Box 109)
  - USDA Publications, undated; cuid2365; 1 Items (Box 110)
  - USDA Publications, undated; cuid2366; 1 Items (Box 116)
  - Vaccination Protects Chicks from Epidemic Tremor, undated; cuid2367; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Vegetable Garden Soil Test Recommendations, undated; cuid2368; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Vegetable Gardening, undated; cuid2369; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Vegetables for Variety, undated; cuid2370; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Vitamins - College of Agriculture, undated; cuid2371; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Vocational-Technical Education for Agricultural Occupations, 1966/08; cuid2372; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Volunteer Information Provider Program: Providing Information for Caregivers of the Elderly, undated; cuid2373; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Weed Identification Sheets #17-32, undated; cuid2374; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - Weekly and Daily press releases, 1953; cuid2375; 1 Items (Box 142)
  - Weekly and Daily press releases, 1950-1954; cuid2376; 1 Items (Box 143)
  - Weekly Field Reports by E. K. Hibshman, 1912-1916; cuid2377; 1 Items (Box 106)
  - Weekly Field Reports by F. P. Weaver, 1915-1916; cuid2378; 1 Items (Box 106)
  - Welfare-To-Work Program, 2000 (Box 278)
  - What Agricultural Extension Service Has Done for Agriculture, undated; cuid2379; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - What Good Foods Can Do For Us, undated; cuid2380; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - What's Your Aging Quotient?, undated; cuid2381; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - When Your Income Drops, undated; cuid2382; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Who Will Control U.S. Agriculture?, undated; cuid2383; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Why Extension?, undated; cuid2384; 1 Items; Photographic--Slides--Slide Shows (Box 162)
  - Wildlife Technology: Two-Year Major, undated; cuid2385; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Wildlife Technology: A 2-Year Major in the School of Forest Resources - Dubois Campus, undated; cuid2386; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Winning Food Ideas: A Recipe Booklet, undated; cuid2387; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Woodworking for Wildlife - Homes for Birds and Mammals, undated; cuid2388; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Workshop and Seminar Material, undated; cuid2389; 1 Items (Box 110)
  - Workshop on Local Delivery Rate Management and Vehicle Scheduling for the Food Industry, undated; cuid2390; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Workshop on the Determination of Protein Content in Daily Products, 1976/07; cuid2391; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - You Can Help - Solve Community Development Problems, undated; cuid2392; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - You Can Lose Weight the Safe Way, undated; cuid2393; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - You Know the Stork Won't Bring Your Baby!, undated; cuid2394; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Your Flower Garden Soil - College of Agriculture, undated; cuid2395; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Your Lucky Food Clover, undated; cuid2396; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Youth Nutrition Program, undated; cuid2397; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Zettles, Frank Anniversaries and Testimonial Dinners for County Agents, undated; cuid2398; 1 Items (Box 107)
  - Zettles, Frank Audio Tape - Heritage We Share, undated; cuid2399; 1 Items (Box 107)
  - Zettles, Frank Historical Materials, undated; cuid2400; 1 Items (Box 106)
  - Zettles, Frank Historical Materials, undated; cuid2401; 1 Items (Box 107)
  - Zettles, Frank Interviews and Correspondence with Retired Agents, undated; cuid2402; 1 Items (Box 106)
  - Zettles, Frank Programs, Clippings, Historical Photographs and 35mm color slides, undated; cuid2403; 1 Items (Box 107)
  - Zettles, Frank Publications, Reports, Minutes, Clippings and Notes, undated; cuid2404; 1 Items (Box 106)
  - AGRI-Digest, unknown; 1 Sound Discs Located in - GCS/X/04.S06
- 11: Capital Region, 1980-2010
  - 01: General, 1984-2010
    - Accident Report, 1990-2001; cuid2511 (Box 242)
    - Administrative Assistant Conference, 1996-2007; cuid2474 (Box 243)
    - Administrative Fellow, 2001-2005; cuid2508 (Box 242)
    - Administrative Retreat, 2005-2006; cuid2466 (Box 244)
    - Administrative Review, 2006; cuid2467 (Box 244)
    - Ag. Agents Program Planning, 1993-1997; cuid2519 (Box 245)
    - Agricultural Economics in Rural Society, 1990-2000; cuid2515 (Box 245)
    - Agronomy, 1998-2003; cuid2516 (Box 245)
    - Animal Science, 2008; cuid2549 (Box 249)
    - Annual POW Co-chairs, 2007; cuid2492 (Box 242)
    - Budget, 2002-2007; cuid2560 (Box 247)
    - Capital Communication, 1994-1999; cuid2509 (Box 242)
    - Capital Region Conferences, 1994-2007; cuid2473 (Box 243)
    - Community Development Planning Program, 1999-2005; cuid2518 (Box 245)
    - Consumer Horticulture Revenure Course, 1999-2004; cuid2535 (Box 245)
    - Cooperative Extension "Impacts You", 2004-2005; cuid2510 (Box 242)
    - Cost Recovery, 2003-2004; cuid2479 (Box 243)
    - County Extension Director's Meetings, 2004-2009; cuid2539 (Box 246)
    - County Extension Director's Leadership Team Meetings, 2005-2009; cuid2540 (Box 246)
    - County Extension Director's Retreat, 2005; cuid2541 (Box 246)
    - County Extension Directors Search Process, 2004-2006; cuid2513 (Box 242)
    - CREAT (Capital Region Extension Agronomy Team), 2000; cuid2520 (Box 245)
    - CROC Meeting, 2007; cuid2465 (Box 244)
    - Dairy Alliance, undated; cuid2551 (Box 249)
    - Dairy and Animal Science Team, 1998-2006; cuid2559 (Box 249)
    - Dairy Options Pilot Program, 1998-2001; cuid2555 (Box 249)
    - Dairy Program Planning Committee, 1993, 1998-2004; cuid2556 (Box 249)
    - Dairy Task Force PDA, 2004; cuid2557 (Box 249)
    - Dean's Meeting, 2004-2005; cuid2469 (Box 244)
    - Director of Dairy Industrial Relations, 1996-2000; cuid2550 (Box 249)
    - Diversity Framework, 2005; cuid2485 (Box 242)
    - E-Business, E-Commerce, E-Government, 2001-2002; cuid2532 (Box 245)
    - Educational Vacancy Map, 2007; cuid2463 (Box 244)
    - Employment Grib, 2001-2007; cuid2482 (Box 242)
    - Executive Leadership Meetings and Retreats, 2005-2007; cuid2471 (Box 244)
    - Food Safety Certification Program, 2000-2004; cuid2480 (Box 243)
    - Farm and Facility Report- Biglerville Fruit Research Center, 2006; cuid2524 (Box 245)
    - Food Science, 1998-2002; cuid2553 (Box 249)
    - Foot and mouth disease, 2000-2001; cuid2554 (Box 249)
    - 4-H A-100, 1989, 1999-2007; cuid2544 (Box 249)
    - 4-H and Youth, 2000-2008; cuid2547 (Box 249)
    - 4-H Centennial, 2001-2002; cuid2548 (Box 249)
    - 4-H Horse Program Strategic Plan, 2006; cuid2462 (Box 244)
    - 4-H Regional Development Committee, 1991-2004; cuid2545 (Box 249)
    - 4-H Strategic Planning, 2001; cuid2546 (Box 249)
    - FREC Advisory Committee, 2002-2006; cuid2522 (Box 245)
    - FREC Strategic Planning, 2000; cuid2521 (Box 245)
    - Fruit Center for Excellence, 2006; cuid2525 (Box 245)
    - Goodling, Rob, 2009; cuid2497 (Box 242)
    - Gregory, Martha, 2007; cuid2500 (Box 242)
    - Hall, Phil, 2008; cuid2496 (Box 242)
    - Horticulture Agents Meeting, 1990-1993; cuid2537 (Box 245)
    - Horticulture Diagnostic Imaging System, 2002-2003; cuid2533 (Box 245)
    - Horticulture Program Planning, 1996-2004; cuid2536 (Box 245)
    - Horticulture Therapy, 1990; cuid2538 (Box 245)
    - Industry Partnership Workshop, 2007; cuid2464 (Box 244)
    - In-house grants, 2002-2005; cuid2484 (Box 242)
    - Integrated Pest Management, 1994-2001; cuid2531 (Box 245)
    - John Schwartz Leadership Award, 2002-2008; cuid2504 (Box 242)
    - Knoll. Karen, 2008; cuid2498 (Box 242)
    - Master Gardner, 1990-2005; cuid2527 (Box 245)
    - Master Gardner Concerns, 1996-1998; cuid2528 (Box 245)
    - Minority Internship, 2001; cuid2512 (Box 242)
    - Myers, Kristy, 2008; cuid2499 (Box 242)
    - Nina Redding, 2001; cuid2507 (Box 242)
    - NSO, 2004; cuid2503 (Box 242)
    - Nutrient Management Education, 1991-2000; cuid2543 (Box 247)
    - Nutrient Management Proposal, 2003-2004; cuid2542 (Box 247)
    - Origin of Extension, undated; cuid2491 (Box 242)
    - Park to Plow- No-till, 2005-2007; cuid2490 (Box 242)
    - PCCEA Executive Board Meeting, 2006; cuid2476 (Box 243)
    - PCCEA Meeting, 2007; cuid2493 (Box 242)
    - PCCEA Meetings, 1990-2004; cuid2478 (Box 243)
    - PCCEA (PA Council of Cooperative Extension Association), 2005; cuid2475 (Box 243)
    - PCCEA State Board Meeting, 2005, 2007; cuid2477 (Box 243)
    - Penn State Flower Trial Report, 2001; cuid2534 (Box 245)
    - Pequea-Mill Creek, 1991-2001; cuid2552 (Box 249)
    - Pesticide Education Certification, 1990-1999; cuid2461 (Box 244)
    - Pesticide Education Fund, 2005-2007; cuid2487 (Box 242)
    - Pesticide Education Program, 2005; cuid2517 (Box 245)
    - Philadelphia Flower Show, 1987-2007; cuid2526 (Box 245)
    - Photographs, undated; cuid2472 (Box 243)
    - Plum Pox Virus, 1999-2004; cuid2523 (Box 245)
    - Promotion Assessment, 2007-2009; cuid2501 (Box 242)
    - Promotion Letters, 2002-2007; cuid2502 (Box 242)
    - PROSPER-Becky, 2002-2009; cuid2488 (Box 242)
    - PROSPER-Ed, 2002-2009; cuid2489 (Box 242)
    - PSU Harrisburg Opening, 1990; cuid2483 (Box 242)
    - Regional Directors Meetings, 2005-2007; cuid2470 (Box 244)
    - Resource Conservation and Development, 1992-2003; cuid2530 (Box 245)
    - Seed Grant-Tara & Matt, 2006-2007; cuid2486 (Box 242)
    - State proceedings, 2005-2010; cuid2494 (Box 242)
    - Statewide promotion training, 2001-2006; cuid2495 (Box 242)
    - Strategic Plan, 1992-1996, 1999, 2004; cuid2481 (Box 243)
    - Team Dairy, 2000-2002; cuid2558 (Box 249)
    - Tilling the Soil of Opportunity, 2002-2003; cuid2514 (Box 245)
    - Urban Forestry, 1991-1997; cuid2529 (Box 245)
    - Watts, Laura, 2003; cuid2506 (Box 242)
    - Wiker, Nancy, 2005; cuid2505 (Box 242)
    - Yourth Development/ 4-H Coordination, 2007; cuid2468 (Box 244)
  - 02: Adams County, 1980-2007
    - Big B-A-A Goat Club, 1999-2001; cuid2565 (Box 248)
    - Budget/Finance, 1995-2002; cuid2564 (Box 248)
    - Dubbs Incident, 2003; cuid2562 (Box 248)
    - Executive Committee/Board of Directors, 2003-2004; cuid2566 (Box 248)
    - Overview, 1983-2000; cuid2561 (Box 248)
    - Reports/Meetings, 1980-2007; cuid2563 (Box 248)
    - Staffing, 2002; cuid2567 (Box 248)
  - 03: Cumberland County, 1984-2007
    - Duanne Duncan- personal, 1994; cuid2568 (Box 248)
    - Executive Committee/Board of Directors, 2004-2006; cuid2572 (Box 248)
    - FOCA, 2002-2004; cuid2573 (Box 248)
    - Overview, 1984-2006; cuid2570 (Box 248)
    - Reports/Meetings/Accomplishments, 1986-2007; cuid2571 (Box 248)
    - Strasburgh, 2002; cuid2569 (Box 248)
    - Team Building, 1996; cuid2574 (Box 248)
  - 04: Dauphin County, 1985-2006
    - Budget/Finances, 1992, 2002-2004; cuid2578 (Box 248)
    - Executive Committee/Board of Directors, 2002; cuid2579 (Box 248)
    - IPM, 1990-1995; cuid2580 (Box 248)
    - Micheal, A., 1990-1995; cuid2576 (Box 248)
    - Overview, 1990-1993; cuid2575 (Box 248)
    - Reports/Meetings/Accomplishments, 1986-2006; cuid2577 (Box 248)
  - 05: Franklin County, 1985-2006
    - Budget/Finances, 1993-2006; cuid2584 (Box 248)
    - Executive Committee/Board of Directors, 2002; cuid2586 (Box 248)
    - Franklin Tobacco, 2004-2005; cuid2587 (Box 248)
    - New building, 2000; cuid2585 (Box 248)
    - Overview, 1985-2003; cuid2581 (Box 248)
    - Pugh Therapeutic Horse, 2002; cuid2582 (Box 248)
    - Reports/Meetings/Accomplishments, 1985-2006; cuid2583 (Box 248)
    - Staff Reports, 2003; cuid2588 (Box 248)
  - 06: Lancaster County, 1980-2007
    - Annual Meeting, 2003, 2007; cuid2592 (Box 247)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-2001; cuid2591 (Box 247)
    - Budget/Financial, 1992-1999, 1995-2003; cuid2594 (Box 247)
    - Correspondence/Statistics, 1987-1989; cuid2593 (Box 247)
    - Direction Handbook, 1991; cuid2589 (Box 247)
    - Executive Committee/Board of Directors, 2003-2007; cuid2596 (Box 247)
    - 4-H, 1987-2002; cuid2590 (Box 247)
    - 4-H trip to Poland, 1999-2000; cuid2595 (Box 247)
  - 07: Lebanon County, 1987-2009
    - Activities, 1987; cuid2598 (Box 247)
    - Budget/Finances, 1995-2003; cuid2600 (Box 247)
    - County Fair, 1987; cuid2597 (Box 247)
    - Executive Committe/Board of Directors, 2004-2007; cuid2601 (Box 247)
    - Reports/Meetings, 1987-2005; cuid2599 (Box 247)
  - 08: Perry County, 1980-2009
    - Budget/Finances, 1980-2009; cuid2604 (Box 247)
    - Executive Committee/Board of Directors, 1986-2006; cuid2605 (Box 247)
    - News, 2004; cuid2602 (Box 247)
    - Reports/Meetings, 1992-1998; cuid2603 (Box 247)
  - 09: York County, 1986-2008
    - Annual Reports, 1986-1999; cuid2609 (Box 243)
    - Budget/Finances, 2000-2003; cuid2614 (Box 243)
    - Bylaws, 1999; cuid2615 (Box 243)
    - Clippings and Articles, 1985-2004; cuid2607 (Box 243)
    - Committee and Board Meetings, 1999-2003; cuid2608 (Box 243)
    - 4-H Reorganization, 1998-2000; cuid2616 (Box 243)
    - Future of Agriculture in York County, 2004; cuid2613 (Box 243)
    - Home Skills Counselor Proposal, 1991; cuid2606 (Box 243)
    - Horn Farm, undated; cuid2611 (Box 243)
    - West Nile Virus Workers, 2008; cuid2610 (Box 243)
    - York Fair Complaint- Hog Sale, 1997; cuid2612 (Box 243)
- Additions
  - Files (Box 165)
  - Files (Box 192)
  - Files (Box 276)